-嗨  -嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
- Hi. - Hey.
我们有点事和你们谈谈
We need to talk about something.
我们觉得
Yeah. We don't feel like
今年我们不能再作东感恩节晚餐了
we can host Thanksgiving this year.
-什么... -你是在开玩笑吧
- What... - Are you kidding?
连带工作  还有领养孩子的压力
Well, it's just with work and the stress of adoption...
我们只是觉得没有精力弄了
...we don't feel like we have the energy.
而且每年都让我们受累
Plus, we don't think it's fair
这不公平
that every year the burden falls on us.
这口气不像你啊
That doesn't sound like you.
这像是莫妮卡的话
That's Monica talking.
不  不  这是我们两个人的决定
No, no, we made this decision together.
你把她放你嘴里的话  又说了一遍
She's putting words in your mouth.
你不应该把话放到我们口中
Don't you put words in people's mouths.
而是把火鸡放到我们口中
You put turkey in people's mouths.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
这可是艾玛的第一个感恩节
This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
才不是...
No, it's not.
不是吗  她什么时候出生的
It's not? When was she born?
我个人认为
Well, personally,
你们是应该休息一下子了
I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
谢谢  菲比
Thank you, Pheebs.
不客气  这样倒好
Sure. It's just as well.
我是说  去年的晚餐也没那么好
I mean, last year wasn't very good.
她已江郎才尽  今年不会更好了
I think she's losing her touch.
什么  你大错特错了  女士
What? You are way off, lady.
是么  真的吗  是么
Am l? Really? Am l?
那你就再做一次感恩节大餐
Well, why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner
证明我错了
and prove me wrong.
你好好想想
Well, think about it.
你这是在跟去年的你比拼
You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
你是在和...自己竞争
You'd be in competition with yourself.
大爱啊
That's my favorite kind.
好吧  今年我们继续
Okay, we are doing this.
别让自己这么容易被左右
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
不关你的事  钱德勒
Stay out of this, Chandler.
这是"我"和"我"之间的事情
This is between me and me.
这件事
We are supposed to
我们应该一起决定啊
make these decisions together.
还记得我给你录的菲尔医生怎么说的么
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil I taped for you?
-嗨  -嗨  感恩节快乐
- Hey. - Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
火鸡殉难日快乐
Happy Needless Turkey-Murder Day.
我从布利克
You guys, I ordered some chocolate pies
订了些巧克力派
from that bakery on Bleeker.
你们能帮我去取回来么
Could you pick them up for me?
你不自己作派吗
You're not making the pies?
不  我不做巧克力派的
I don't make chocolate pies.
我小时候
When I was younger,
参加过一个吃派比赛
I entered this pie-eating contest.
吃得太多了
I ate so many
导致我一想就恶心
that the thought of them makes me sick.
那你赢了没有
Did you at least win the contest?
两分钟吃了12个外加1片
Two minutes, twelve pies and a part of one tin.
好吧  我们4点见
Okay, I'll see you guys at 4.
很让人期待哦
Can't wait.
今年的晚餐一定棒极了
This dinner is gonna be so great.
去年的莫妮卡  我要你好看
In your face, last-year me.
-嗨  瑞秋  -嗯
- Hey, Rach? - Yeah.
艾玛今天的行程是什么
What's Emma doing today?
我们看看啊
Well, let's see,
我只知道她今天要和律师见面
I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer...
然后呢  她要拉个大便
...and then she has to make a very big poop.
怎么了
Why?
我想让她参加婴儿选美
Well, I want to enter her in a baby pageant.
哦  天呐
Oh, my God.
这是我听说过的最让人毛骨悚然的事情了
That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
在你拒绝之前  听我说
Okay, but before you say no,
我朋友苏珊娜带她的孩子参加了
my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
和艾玛比起来
And compared to Emma,
那小家伙就像只小狗
she's a real dog.
哦  菲比  所有孩子都是美丽的
Phoebe, all babies are beautiful.
好吧
Oh, okay.
不  菲比
No. Phoebe,
难道我们只是为了一个奖杯
just the idea of pitting one baby against another...
就把孩子们比来比去
...l mean, you know,
决定谁更漂亮
and judging who's cuter just for a trophy...
还有一千块奖金
And a thousand dollars.
对此我很感兴趣
...is something I'm very interested in.
对了  千万别告诉罗斯
Oh, please, do not tell Ross.
他还是相信
He still believes that
内在的东西才重要
what's on the inside is important.
对了艾玛得
Okay. And Emma needs a cowgirl outfit
穿牛仔装参加比赛
for the competition.
感恩节我上哪儿找牛仔装啊
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
我在想...
Well, I was thinking--
把乔伊的椰菜娃娃的衣服扒了
Take the clothes off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
又有人把指挥棒给掉了
Did someone drop the baton again?
为什么从堪萨斯那么老远来
Why come all the way from Kansas
就为了做这个
to do that?
老娘不是越来越老  而是越来越好
I don't get older, I just get better.
你知道我刚想到什么
You know what just occurred to me?
这可能是最后一次
This could be our last Thanksgiving
只有我们两个人一起过感恩节了
just the two of us.
我是说  我们很快就会有个孩子了
I mean, we could be getting a baby soon.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
有人会选择我们的
Somebody's gonna pick us.
可是这几周
But we haven't heard a thing
我们都没收到领养消息
from the adoption agency.
我告诉你  肯定会的
I'm telling you, it's gonna happen.
明年会是
Next year,
你我还有小海明威·宾
it's gonna be you, me and little Hemingway Bing.
干嘛  他是我最喜欢的作家
What? He's my favorite author.
说出他一本书的名字
Name one of his books.
《企业》
The Firm?
好吧  火鸡已经在烤箱里了
Okay, let's see. Okay, the turkey's in the oven.
添料也准备好了
The stuffing is ready.
你知道么
You know,
你总是自己弄这些东西
you always cook this meal all by yourself.
今年让我帮帮你吧
Let me help this year.
钱德勒  这太好了
Oh, Chandler, that's sweet.
但你不用一直按菲尔医生说的做
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
我是认真的  让我做点什么吧
I'm serious, let me do something.
不是给火鸡填馅  做点不难的东西  .
Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
我想想...
Okay, let's see.
啊  酸梅酱
Oh, the cranberry sauce.
很容易做
It's easy to make,
而且大家也不是很在意那东西
and no one really cares about it.
还有呢
Tell me more.
我去对门儿检查别的
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall.
你先把这个洗干净吧
You start by washing these.
别用洗涤剂
Not with soap!
你肯定没吃过我沐浴液洗过的土豆
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
嘿  猜猜乔伊拿到了什么
Hi. Hey, guess what Joey has.
三张今天纽约流浪者的票
Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
兄弟  我是让他猜的
Dude, I wanted him to guess.
哦  天哪
Oh, my God.
是啊  而且都是好座位哦
Yeah, they're great seats too.
猜猜什么位置
Guess where they are.
正中间
Center ice.
我是不是和你有什么过节
Did I do something to you?
比赛一点开始
The game's at 1.
怎样
So?
晚饭四点开始  我们赶不回来的
Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back.
那我们就提前退场
So we'll leave before it's over.
我们会准时回来的
We'll be back in time.
你现在这么说
You said that now.
可是到时候必定要花很多时间回来的
But it could take us a long time to get back home.
另外乔伊可能会迷路
Plus, Joey could get lost
他们还得喊我们把他领会来
and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
老兄  事不过三
Dude, two times that happened!
莫妮卡为了做晚饭忙了一整天
Look, Monica's been working hard all day.
她一开始的时候是不想做的
She didn't want to host in the first place.
我们不该去的
We shouldn't go.
他说得没错儿
He's right, man.
好吧  那么四点钟见
Yeah, I guess. So we'll see you at 4.
嗯
Okay.
准备好品尝
And get ready to taste
我的特制酸梅酱哦
my very special cranberries.
或者  应该叫做"钱式酸梅"
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
伙计  你真够搞笑的
That's some gentle comedy, dude.
我们还是要去看比赛的  对吧
We're still going to the game, right?
是的
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
菲比  我想走了
Phoebe, listen, I think we gotta go.
这地方让我坐立不安
This place is freaking me out.
你看到那边那个人了么
I've been watching this guy over there.
我可不认为他带来的是个孩子
I don't think he came with a kid.
但你现在不能离开啊
But we can't leave now.
有一个叫黑利的小孩
There was this one baby, Haley,
是夺冠的大热门
who was favored to win...
得了哮喘  不得不待在家里
...she got croup, so she had to stay home.
这次比赛才大开方便之门  家长们
This competition just blew wide-open, folks.
菲比  这太奇怪了
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
我看见一个一岁的小孩穿连裤袜
I just saw a 1 -year-old with pantyhose on.
我知道  我们准备的确实不够充分
Oh, I know. We should've been more prepared.
没事儿  我觉得
It's okay. Now, the way I see it,
咱们最有力的竞争对手是卡梅伦
our real competition now is Cameron.
天呐  她的衣服被脱掉了
My God, they just took her sweater off.
看他的手臂  你好  米其林先生
Look at those arms. Hello, Michelin Man.
菲比
Phoebe, come on.
已经都三点了
You know what, it's already 3:00.
他们还没有评审到艾玛这一组
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet.
我们该走了  回去吃饭
We got dinner.
但是艾玛的条件都具备了
But Emma's got what it takes.
她一定能走到最后
She could go all the way!
菲比  冷静点
Phoebe, you have to calm down.
好吧
Okay.
瑞秋  三州交界地区
Rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area
最漂亮的宝贝们都在这里了
are in this room right now.
而我听见一个评审说
I overheard a judge say
没人比得过艾玛
that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
-真的么  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
你听见他们这么说
You heard him say that?
对
Yeah.
好吧  那就让我们
All right. Okay. All right,
给其他的孩子们一点悲惨的回忆
let's give these babies something to cry about.
太好了  开工吧
Good. Let's get down to business.
艾玛需要化妆
Emma needs some makeup.
什么
What?
不化妆跟其它孩子比起来会逊色三分的
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
菲比  我不会让你给我的孩子化妆的
No, Phoebe, I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
为什么不
Why not?
因为我已经给她化过了
Because I already did.
太逊了  快下场吧  你个白痴
You suck! Get off the ice, you idiot!
-太精彩了  -没错  耶
- What a game. - I know. Yeah.
钱德勒错过了这场比赛真遗憾啊
I can't believe Chandler's missing this.
我也替他觉得遗憾
I'm sorry he's not here.
但我不得不说
But I gotta say,
我真的很喜欢这个"玉米片"座
I am really enjoying nacho chair.
嗯  要是你不总是把我的手打开
Yeah, I'd probably enjoy it more
我也许会更喜欢些
if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
这位置太棒了
These seats are great.
是啊  没错
I know, I know.
上次在这看假期冰上节目
When I was here for "Holidays on lce" ...
座位太远了
...l was sitting so far away,
关颖珊根本就看不到我举的条幅
Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
我们该走了啦
We'd better get going.
现在不走  回去吃饭就晚了
If we don't leave now, we're gonna be late.
可比赛太精彩了
But it's a tie game.
回去晚点应该可以吧
So we're a little late.
女生们会在那的
The girls will be there.
再进一个球再走啦
Let's just stay for one more goal.
-不好吧  -再有人打一架
- I don't know. - One more fight.
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
大家都哪里去了
Where is everybody?
他们迟到了45分钟
They're 45 minutes late.
我真不敢相信他们还没来
I can't believe they're not here.
我那么辛苦这一天是为了什么
I slave and I slave for what?
他们毁了我的酸梅酱日
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
我们迟到了多久
How late are we?
45分钟
Forty-five minutes.
-给  -好的.
- Here. - Okay.
瑞秋和菲比应该已经到了
Rachel and Phoebe are already there,
所以他们可能已经开始了
so they probably started without us.
我们溜进去
We could just slip in,
这样谁都不会注意我们的
and no one needs to know where we were.
你不把这个泡沫大手指扔掉么
You may want to lose the foam finger.
哦  才不呢
Oh, no, no, no.
你只是想把它套在你手上
You just want to put it on your hand.
你们没在里面
You're not at Thanksgiving?
没  我们迟到了
No, we're late.
你们在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我们也迟到了
We're late too.
我们本以为我们可以迟到
We figured we could be late
因为你们会准时到
because you'd be on time.
别用这个指着我  姓崔的
Don't point that thing at me, Tribbiani.
那...里面没人
So nobody's here?
莫妮卡会杀了我们的
Monica's gonna kill us.
你们到什么地方去了
Yeah, where were you?
奖杯怎么来的
Yeah, what's with the trophy?
嗯  我们去参加拼字大赛了
Well, we were at a spelling bee.
我赢了
And I won.
你在感恩节这天
You won an adult
赢得了一场成人拼字游戏
Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
是  Y-E-S  是
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
让我看看...
Let me see this.
纽约区超级无敌小可爱
"Grand Supreme Little Darling, New York Division"?
那便是我
That's me.
你们让艾玛参加了选美比赛
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
而且看起来她还给她化了妆
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
等等...
Wait a second...
我好像在什么地方见过这身牛仔...
Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
无法置信
I can't believe this.
她是我们的女儿
She's our daughter.
你把她当成观赏狗一样
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog
不可饶恕
is inexcusable.
她为我们赢得了一千美元
She won a thousand dollars.
这比赛是一年一次的吗
So this is an annual thing?
啊  这是艾莉西亚·梅·埃默里的服装
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
伙计们  有人在里面
Guys, there are people in there
要发火了
who are not getting any happier.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我不知道  你们想办法
I don't know, you guys figure it out.
我先把艾玛送回去睡觉
I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
哦  瑞秋  你进去
And, Rach, while you're in there,
给艾莉西亚·梅穿件衣服
throw something on Alicia May.
好吧  我们该怎么说
All right, what are we gonna say?
我们可以说  我们被抢劫了
We'll say that we were mugged.
当有人被抢了的时候
You can't get mad at someone
你怎么还会生他气
who's been mugged.
不错  但你看起来不像被抢过
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
不像  这样才像
No. Here.
嘿
Hey!
你有没有听到什么
Do you hear something?
-他们都在外面  -让我看看
- They're out there. - Let me see.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
他们迟到了一小时
They're an hour late,
还在那里聊天
and they're just standing there talking.
一切都乱套了
Everything's so distorted.
乔伊有只大手
It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
上面写"流浪者"
That says "Rangers" on it.
他们去看比赛了
They went to the game.
这下我饶不了他们
Oh, they are in for a world of pain.
罗斯的衬衫撕坏了
Ross' shirt is torn.
他们不但迟到  而且衣衫不整
They're late and they're sloppy.
好了  艾玛睡下了
All right, Emma's napping.
你的衬衫怎么了
What happened to your shirt?
我被抢了
I got mugged,
他们还抢走了我的口袋
and they stole my pocket.
我们是在找借口
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
这样如何
How about this?
我们可以说
We could say that
莫妮卡告诉我们是5点  而不是4点
Monica told us 5:00, not 4:00.
这样我们就没迟到而且很准时
That way we're right on time.
或者  我们可以在房间里藏些迷药
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment
打电话让警察把她抓了
and call the cops on her.
嗯  这的确是个
That would be a good way
下迷药的好办法
to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
你可以就说她说的是5点
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
保持自然些
We'll just act casual.
所以我们根本没有迟到
We're not late, we're right on time.
"我们知道你们在外面"
"We know you're out there."
你觉得这是谁写的
Who do you think it's from?
天啊  糟了  简直太糟了
Oh, God, this is bad. This is so bad.
好吧  让我们进去面对他们吧
Well, let's just go in there and face them.
我不要先进去
I'm not going in first.
莫妮卡前额上的青筋肯定快爆裂了
I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
我也讨厌啊
I hate that thing.
那张脸就像扭曲的闪电一样
It's like a bolt of lightning.
我有主意了
I have an idea.
我们可以玩石头剪子布
Why don't we play Rock, Paper, Scissors,
输了的先进去
and whoever loses, goes in first.
-好吧  我参加  -准备
- All right, I'm in. - Ready.
啊  我赢了
I win.
这是什么
What is that?
火焰  赢过一切
That's fire. It beats everything.
真的么  能赢过一个水球么
Oh, really? Does it beat water balloon?
好极了  菲比·布菲  玩得真好
Well-played, Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
好啦好啦
All right, enough,
让我们一起进去算了
let's all go in at the same time.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
锁住了
It's locked.
什么  他们现在倒把门锁上了
What? Oh, sure, now they lock it.
当他们在沙发上做爱时
When they're having sex
就像是在说
on the couch, it's like:
"快进来  快进来  我的屁股上毛好多  "
"Come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
好吧  别闹了  里面的两位
All right, come on. All right, you guys,
很抱歉我们迟到了
we're so sorry we're late.
让我们进去一起吃晚餐吧
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
不  东西都凉了
No, everything's cold.
火鸡干了  馅也松了
The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
嗯  而且那碗酸梅酱也……
Yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's--
酸梅酱怎么了
What happens to cranberry sauce?
没事儿  很好
Nothing, it's fine.
哦  谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
好啦  伙计们  真的抱歉
Come on, you guys, we're sorry.
回来的路上  地铁坏了
Our subway broke down.
说谎
That's a lie!
你们去看比赛了
You went to the game.
我能看到乔伊的手
I can see Joey's hand.
我说过了让你把它扔掉了
For the love of God, take it off!
伙计们  我们是否迟到了并不重要
Guys, it doesn't matter why we're late.
重要的是我们都到了
We're all here now.
让我们进去
Please let us in so we can
吃美味的火鸡吧
have some of your delicious turkey.
我曾经做梦
I had a dream once
传真机可以这样
about a fax machine that did that.
这就是你们能得的火鸡
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
怎么决定谁吃
How are we gonna decide who gets this?
水球
Water balloon!
我们该怎么办啊
What are we gonna do?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
哦  对了  我想起来了
I just remembered,
我们有吃的了
we do have something to eat.
今天早晨莫妮卡
Monica put something
放了点东西在炉子里面
in our oven this morning.
嘿  动了它你们会后悔的
You touch that, and you will be sorry!
伙计们  最好听她的
Guys, I'd listen to her.
她的血管涨到前所未有的大
The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
天呐  是甘蓝菜
Oh, my God, it's Brussels sprouts!
这是什么嘛  不能吃的
That's worse than no food.
啊哈  你们只有莫妮卡的发臭甘蓝菜
All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
发臭的
Stinky?
请让我呆在门的这一边
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
对了  我还有以前的钥匙呢
Oh, I know! I still have my old key.
我们可以直接把门打开
We can just unlock the door.
我不觉得这是个好主意
I don't know if that's a good idea.
他们明显不想和我们在一起
They don't wanna be with us.
你知道么
You know what.
我也不想和他们一起
I don't wanna be with them either...
但今天是感恩节
...but it's Thanksgiving,
不想在一起也要在一起
and we should not want to be together together.
让我们进去
If I could just get in there,
面对面的道歉吧
make a face-to-face apology...
看到我的眼睛
...look them in the eye,
他们就会原谅我的
I could get them to forgive us.
我不确定
I don't know.
我告诉你...
I'm telling you...
我做得到
...l can do it.
嗯  他做得到
Yeah, he can do it.
看起来太美味了
It all looks so beautiful.
那火鸡  那填料
The turkey, the stuffing.
那酸梅酱呢
The cranberries.
够了  猴子都会做
Enough! A monkey could've made them.
听我说  我们真得很抱歉
Hey, listen, guys, we feel really terrible.
他又来那什么"目光接触"了
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
别看他
Don't look at him.
听我说  伙计们
Come on, you guys.
我们想让你们了解  我们真的  真的很抱歉
We want you to know we're very, very sorry.
对吧  伙计们
Right, guys?
-真的很抱歉  -非常  对不起
- I feel terrible. - Oh, so sorry.
我们别毁掉这美好的一天啊
But let's not ruin this day.
你们如此之辛劳
You've worked so hard.
让我们忘了这件事
Let's move past this
一起吃一顿美好的晚餐吧
and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?
那些漂浮着的脑袋好像说得没错
The floating heads do make a good point.
是啊  他们真的好像很抱歉
Yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.
非常抱歉
So bad.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  你们两个去拿甜品来
Okay, you two go get the dessert,
我让你们进来
and I'll let you in.
甜品
Dessert?
是啊  我让你和菲比去取派
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies.
你们记得的  对吧
You did remember, right?
"派"啊  我们以为是"奖"
Pies. Oh, we thought you said "prize."
给你
Here.
超级无敌小可爱
"Grand Supreme Little Darling"?
恭喜
Congratulations!
天呐  你忘了拿派
Oh, my God, you forgot the pies?
真不敢相信
Well, I cannot believe this.
你们强迫我做饭
You forced me to make dinner,
又迟到一小时
you're an hour late...
居然还忘记了
...and you forget the one little thing
我叫你们做的那一点点小事
that I asked you to do.
真的  女孩子们  这就是你们不对了
Really, girls, not cool.
好吧  你们男人又好到哪里去
Well, you man-heads aren't any better.
你们说谎  去看比赛
You lied about going to the game.
明知道会迟到
You knew it'd make you late,
还坚持要去
and you went anyway.
我有点烦了
Hey, I'm getting a little tired of this.
我们都道歉了
We said we're sorry.
今天是感恩节
It's Thanksgiving, for Pete's sakes!
是原谅之日
A day of forgiveness.
是感激之日吧
It's a day to be thankful.
小心我上去敲你
Don't make me come up there!
现在道歉太晚了
It's too late for apologies.
好吧  我们走
Fine, let's just go.
我们可以不在这里吃饭
I don't need your stupid dinner.
如果你没流口水的话
That would be a lot more convincing
你的话可能更可信点
if you weren't drooling.
哦  原来是你的口水
Oh, is that what that is?
对不起
Sorry.
伙计们  我们自己准备感恩节晚餐吧
Come on, you guys, let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
好  我做饭
Yeah, I'll cook.
好  出去吃
Yeah, let's go out.
你们三个  感恩节快乐
Yeah, you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
我们三个
The three of us?
你  钱德勒  还有你的"血管"
Yeah. You, Chan and the vein.
啊  我被卡住了
I'm stuck.
乔伊  这招不管用的
Joey, that is not gonna work.
不  我是认真的
No, seriously.
我真的被卡住了
I'm really wedged in here.
我把你拉出来
I'll pull you through.
好
Okay.
住手
Stop.
我担心会弄伤我的头
I'm worried about damaging my head.
现在说太晚了
It's a little late for that.
快点  帮帮忙啊
Hurry up, you gotta do something.
这不会改变什么的
All right, well, this does not change anything.
我们需要点东西
We need to get something
让他两边的脸润滑一些
to grease the sides of his face
我们有火鸡汁
We got turkey grease.
拿来
Bring it.
我很抱歉
I just want to say that I'm sorry
还把"血管"说成了一个人
I referred to the vein as a separate person.
倒了
Here you go.
味道不错
Oh, that smells good.
-好了吗  -好  试试看
- Okay? - Okay, try it.
没用
It isn't working.
我们必须把链条卸下来了
We're gonna have to unscrew the chain.
快点  我都感觉不到我的耳朵了
Hurry, I can't feel my ears.
你曾经感觉到过耳朵么
Can you ever feel your ears?
有意思
Interesting.
钱德勒  你的工具哪里去了
Chandler, where are your tools?
啊  我把他们落到推土机上了
Oh, I left them on my bulldozer.
我根本也没有工具啊
I don't have tools.
我有  但被瑞秋借去了
Well, I do, but Rachel borrowed them.
我借给了罗斯
I lent them to Ross.
我给了乔伊
I gave them to Joey.
我留在车库了
I left them at the park.
还真忍不住想逗他
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
我早就给他裤子里放了甘蓝菜
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
很好
Nice.
好  我去接电话
Okay, I have to get that.
当我回来的时候
Now, when I get back,
我希望你和你的朋友们已经离开了
I want you and your friends to be gone.
感恩节完了
Thanksgiving is over.
"血管"说话了
The vein has spoken.
我的头真的被卡住了
It's really starting to hurt.
好吧  我会拉门
Look, I'm gonna pull on the door...
然后你们努力推
...and you guys push.
这样可能他就有足够的空隙出来了  好吧
Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay?
好  推吧
Okay, so push.
等下
Just a sec.
我们正忙着
We're kind of in the middle of something here.
别往我的裤子里面放东西
Hey, stop putting things down my pants.
来吧  伙计们  推吧
Come on, guys, push!
来  推  推  推
Yeah, come on, push!
推  推
Push! Push!
我的酸梅酱
My cranberries!
我全身都是吃的了
Man, I got food all over me.
真不敢相信会这样
I can't believe what you did.
莫妮卡会杀了你的
Monica's gonna kill you.
看  看  看
Look! Look! Look
这个"漂脑袋"做了什么
what the-- Look what the floating heads did!
没关系
I don't care.
怎么了
What's going on?
是领养中心处打来的
That was the adoption agency.
然后
And?
我们可以领养孩子了
We're getting a baby!
真的么
Are you serious?!
有个俄亥俄州的孕妇
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio,
选了我们
and she picked us.
天呐  太棒了
Oh, my God, that's great!
难以置信
That's incredible.
太为你们高兴了
I'm so happy for you.
今年的感恩节比去年好太多了
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
敬莫妮卡和钱德勒
To Monica and Chandler
还有那俄亥俄州的不小心怀孕的女孩
and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
你们两个终于要有孩子了
I'm just so happy
这真让我高兴
you guys are finally getting a kid.
你们没考虑过去游行
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
真不敢相信他们打电话来了
I can't believe they called.
我们就会有孩子了
I mean, we're actually getting a baby.
我能体会你们的感受
I know how you feel.
-真的么  -当然啦
- Really? - Sure.
买艾莉西亚·梅·埃默里时
I went through the exact same thing
我经历过完全相同的事情
with Alicia May Emory.
那种期待  那种迷茫
The waiting, the wondering.
直到有一天
Then one day,
我接到了玩具公司的电话
I get that call from Toys"R"Us.
她又有货了
She was in stock.
确实"完全相同"
That is the exact same thing.